Shelly, come on!
(Mrs Cooper(off):)Your sister's fully dilated
(Mrs Cooper(off):)and she wants
a nice family picture
before there's blood everywhere!
(Sheldon:)Oh, boy.
(Sheldon:)I picked the wrong day
to wear my good robot T-shirt.
(Raj:)If you were having Sheldon's baby
(Raj:)would you really want him
in the room?
(Penny:)Yeah, if he's in the room
when they're making the baby,
(Penny:)I'll give you ten dollars.
(Bernadette:)Hey, I brought over
It's a Wonderful Life
(Bernadette:)if you guys want to watch it later.
(Amy:)-Oh, I love that movie.
-I've never seen it.
(Stuart:)-Me neither.
-It's great.
It's Christmas time and
Jimmy Stewart's really depressed
(Amy:)and he's gonna jump
off a bridge and kill himself...
(Stuart:)Don't need to see it.
Living it.
(Bernadette:)But then he gets to see
what the world
(Bernadette:)would be like
if he'd never been born.
(Penny:)Hey, you ever imagine
what that would be like?
(Penny:)Not being born?
(Leonard:)What do you think?
(Amy:)You make jokes about Sheldon,
(Amy:)but if it weren't for him,